<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"></rss><channel><title>MajorDan</title><atom:link href="http://TheMajorDan.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><link>http://TheMajorDan.github.io</link><description>Give me liberty, or give me death!</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 15:00:00 -0400</pubDate><language>en</language><item><title>The French Election And Globalism</title><link>http://TheMajorDan.github.io/articles/french-election-globalism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2017 15:00:00 -0400</pubDate><guid isPermaLink="true">http://TheMajorDan.github.io/articles/french-election-globalism/</guid><author></author><description>&lt;p&gt;French presidential candidate Marine Le Pen said “France Will Be Led By a Woman, Me or Mrs. Merkel.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is an important statement because globalism is trying to keep what little influence is has left in the wake of the Brexit and the 2016 U.S. Presidential election. We saw in 2016 &lt;span class=&quot;more&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; where the main stream media were the sock puppets of the global elite, trying to “install” Hillary Clinton as the President by targeting an indifferent and spiritless voter base.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the 2016 election, I talked with a number of people didn’t feel connected in any way to either candidate, but said they were most likely to vote Clinton. When asked why, most would numbly respond, stating that everything they heard on the “news” made her out to be the better choice. I would then ask where they get their news from, and every time they would cite one of the big MSM outlets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The main stream media would consistently prop Hillary Clinton up as some glorious leader, and Americans who didn’t research the candidates on their own would start to believe the rhetoric coming from the muck machine known as the MSM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m seeing the same thing happening in France where Macron is being painted as some savior of the French people, while Le Pen blasts Macron for seeking permission from Merkel before doing anything. If he is in fact elected, Merkel will be in control of France.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, like Trump in 2016, Le Pen has a fired-up &amp;amp; spirited base that has seen the wildfire of Nationalism sweeping the Western world, and they want their own slice of the pie that is sovereignty–much to the dismay of the global elite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am personally very excited for the French people at this juncture, and would love to see a Frexit take place in the coming years. Let’s put yet another nail in the coffin of the global trash trying to run the world with unelected, unaccountable leaders!&lt;/p&gt;
</description></item></channel>